comicbookplus.com 2019-10-18

# Privacy Policy - Comic Book Plus

You are WELCOME to enjoy our site & read ALL our books online. But to download & join our forum please create a FREE account or login

## Links To Other Web Sites

We may make content or services from other Web sites (both affiliated and unaffiliated) available to you from links located on our Web site. These other Web sites are not subject to this Privacy Policy. We recommend that you review the privacy policy at each such Web site to determine how that site protects your privacy. 

## Information We Collect

Registration including a username and password is required to use parts of this site. If you contact us we may collect personally identifiable information from you that may include your name, e-mail and similar information. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of thirteen. 

## Web Site Usage Information

We may collect IP addresses and Web site usage information from you when you visit our Web site. This information helps us evaluate how our visitors use and navigate our Web site on an aggregate basis, including the number and frequency of visitors to each Web page, and the length of their visits. 

## How We May Use Information Collected

We may use information in the following ways: 

For the purposes for which you specifically provided the information including, for example, to respond to a request for information.

Except as specifically set forth in this Privacy Policy, we will not share your personally identifiable information.

We may disclose and use personally identifiable information in special circumstances where it is necessary under the law (for example, when necessary to protect our or a third party's intellectual property or proprietary rights) or when we, in our sole discretion, believe it is necessary or appropriate, in connection with a sale or transfer of some or all of our assets in the Web site or our services. We may also disclose or use your personal information when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires us to do so. 

## Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that is sent by a Web site and stored on your hard drive or temporarily in your computer's memory. We employ cookie technology to help visitors and subscribers move faster through our site. You can turn off the ability to receive any of these cookies by adjusting the browser in your computer, BUT you should note that if you do so, the functionality of this Web site could be SERIOUSLY affected. If you wish to find out more about cookies, or how to refuse cookies, please visit the Interactive Advertising Bureau's web site at [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense and Amazon.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology in the advertisements and links that appear on ComicBookPlus.com sent directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

ComicBookPlus.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. ComicBookPlus.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

## Special Note About Google Advertising

Any advertisements served by Google, Inc., and affiliated companies may be controlled using cookies. These cookies allow Google to display ads based on your visits to this site and other sites that use Google advertising services. Learn how to opt out of Google's cookie usage. As mentioned above, any tracking done by Google through cookies and other mechanisms is subject to Google's own privacy policies.

About Google advertising: What is the DoubleClick DART cookie? The DoubleClick DART cookie is used by Google in the ads served on publisher websites displaying AdSense for content ads. When users visit an AdSense publisher's website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user's browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help AdSense publishers better serve and manage the ads on their site(s) and across the web. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy [http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

## Security

The personally identifiable information we collect about you is stored in limited access servers. We will maintain safeguards to protect the security of these servers and your personally identifiable information. 

## Review And Correction

If you would like to review or update any personally identifiable information that we may hold about you, you may contact the following email address: [team@ComicBookPlus.com](mailto:team@ComicBookPlus.com)

## Policy Modifications

When we make any material change to this Privacy Policy, we will inform you by posting a notice on the home page of this site that the policy has been updated and by changing the date on this page noting when the policy was last updated. 

## Comments And Questions

If you have any questions, comments or concerns about our Privacy Policy, you may contact the following email address: [team@ComicBookPlus.com](mailto:team@ComicBookPlus.com)

**Disclaimer:** If you have come to this site to find pirated or illegal material, you will be disappointed! We only hold comic books and images that are in the Public Domain. If you suspect that any of our content may be infringing copyright, then please use our contact page to let us know. So we can investigate further.
